#
# Some quick questions I whipped up
# Source: https://minecraft.gamepedia.com/
#
questions:
  #
  # Entities
  #
  1:
    question: 'What are Creepers scared of?'
    answer:
      - 'ocelot'
      - 'ocelots'
  2:
    question: 'What can you wear to stop Enderman attacking you?'
    answer:
      - 'pumpkin'
      - 'a pumpkin'
  3:
    question: 'What item do you need to breed llamas?'
    answer:
      - 'Hay bales'
  4:
    question: 'How many neutral mobs exist? (1.15)'
    answer:
      - '11'
  5:
    question: 'How many hit points does a Ghast have?'
    answer:
      - '10'
  6:
    question: 'How many mobs are tameable? (1.15)?'
    answer:
      - '9'
  #
  # Items
  #
  7:
    question: 'How many items can you craft with iron ingots? (1.15)'
    answer:
      - '33'
  8:
    question: 'How many music discs are there? (1.15)'
    answer:
      - '12'
  9:
    question: 'On average, how many uses does an anvil survive?'
    answer:
      - '25'
  10:
    question: 'Does chain armor yield iron nuggets when smelted? (1.15)'
    answer:
      - 'yes'
  #
  # Enchants
  #
  11:
    question: 'Are beehives obtainable with silk touch? (1.15)'
    answer:
      - 'yes'
  12:
    question: 'Does a looting enchanted bow yield more drops?'
    answer:
      - 'no'
  13:
    question: 'Name an enchant that conflicts with smite.'
    answer:
      - 'bane of arthropods'
      - 'sharpness'
  14:
    question: 'What is the minimum amount of bookshelfs needed to get level 18 enchants?'
    answer:
      - '7'
  #
  # Minecraft updates
  #
  15:
    question: 'What is the official name of update 1.4?'
    answer:
      - 'Pretty scary update'
  16:
    question: 'What is the official name of update 1.5?'
    answer:
      - 'Redstone update'
  17:
    question: 'What is the official name of update 1.6?'
    answer:
      - 'Horse update'
  18:
    question: 'What is the official name of update 1.7?'
    answer:
      - 'The update that changed the world'
  19:
    question: 'What is the official name of update 1.8?'
    answer:
      - 'Bountiful update'
  20:
    question: 'What is the official name of update 1.9?'
    answer:
      - 'Combat update'
  21:
    question: 'What is the official name of update 1.10?'
    answer:
      - 'Frostburn update'
  22:
    question: 'What is the official name of update 1.11?'
    answer:
      - 'Exploration update'
  23:
    question: 'What is the official name of update 1.12?'
    answer:
      - 'World of color update'
  24:
    question: 'What is the official name of update 1.13?'
    answer:
      - 'Aquatic update'
  25:
    question: 'What is the official name of update 1.14?'
    answer:
      - 'Village and pillage'
  26:
    question: 'What is the official name of update 1.15?'
    answer:
      - 'Buzzy bees'
  56:
    question: 'What is the official name of update 1.16?'
    answer:
      - 'Nether Update'
  27:
    question: 'What minecraft version added desert pyramids?'
    answer:
      - '1.3'
  28:
    question: 'What minecraft version added command blocks?'
    answer:
      - '1.4'
  29:
    question: 'What minecraft version added scoreboards?'
    answer:
      - '1.5'
  30:
    question: 'What minecraft version changed texture packs to resource packs?'
    answer:
      - '1.6'
  31:
    question: 'What minecraft version introduced amplified terrain?'
    answer:
      - '1.7'
  32:
    question: 'What minecraft version added the @e (entity) selector?'
    answer:
      - '1.8'
  33:
    question: 'What minecraft version overhauled the End?'
    answer:
      - '1.9'
  34:
    question: 'What minecraft version introduced auto jump?'
    answer:
      - '1.10'
  35:
    question: 'What minecraft version increased the chat message length to 256 characters?'
    answer:
      - '1.11'
  36:
    question: 'What minecraft version added hotbar saving/loading in creative mode?'
    answer:
      - '1.12'
  37:
    question: 'What minecraft version added datapacks?'
    answer:
      - '1.13'
  38:
    question: 'What minecraft version added suspicious stew?'
    answer:
      - '1.14'
  39:
    question: 'What minecraft version introduced bees?'
    answer:
      - '1.15'
  40:
    question: 'What minecraft version overhauled the Nether?'
    answer:
      - '1.16'
  #
  # Brewing
  #
  41:
    question: 'What item do you use in a brewing stand to create a thick potion?'
    answer:
      - 'glowstone dust'
  42:
    question: 'How many seconds does it take for the regeneration I effect to heal 3 hearts?'
    answer:
      - '15'
  43:
    question: 'What item do you need to create a strength I potion from an awkward potion?'
    answer:
      - 'Blaze powder'
  44:
    question: 'How many seconds does a regular leaping II potion last for?'
    answer:
      - '90'
  #
  # Biomes
  #
  45:
    question: 'How many unused and removed biomes are there in total? (1.15)'
    answer:
      - '7'
  46:
    question: 'Name an overworld biome not required for the adventure time (discover every biomes) advancement. (1.15)'
    answer:
      - 'Dark forest hills'
      - 'Deep ocean'
      - 'Desert hills'
      - 'Desert lakes'
      - 'Eroded badlands'
      - 'Flower forest'
      - 'Frozen ocean'
      - 'Giant spruce tiaga'
      - 'Giant spruce tiaga hills'
      - 'Gravelly mountains'
      - 'Ice spikes'
      - 'Mountains'
      - 'Mushroom field shore'
      - 'Mushroom fields'
      - 'Ocean'
      - 'Shattered savanna'
      - 'Shattered savanna plateau'
      - 'Sunflower plains'
      - 'Swamp hills'
      - 'Tiaga mountains'
      - 'Tall birch forest'
      - 'Tall birch hills'
  47:
    question: 'What is the maximum temperature value a biome can have to allow snowfall?'
    answer:
      - '0.15'
  #
  # Other
  #
  48:
    question: 'What tool do you need to mine a beacon?'
    answer:
      - 'hand'
      - 'none'
  49:
    question: 'How many minecraft editions/games are there?'
    answer:
      - '7'
  50:
    question: 'What minecraft edition/game are you currently playing?'
    answer:
      - 'java'
      - 'java edition'
  51:
    question: 'What is Notch''s real name?'
    answer:
      - 'Markus Persson'
  52:
    question: 'What year was minecraft classic released?'
    answer:
      - '2009'
  53:
    question: 'What year was minecraft''s full release?'
    answer:
      - '2011'
  54:
    question: 'How many minecraft editions have uncensored chat?'
    answer:
      - '1'
  55:
    question: 'What super mario 64 item was the elytra inspired by?'
    answer:
      - 'wing cap'
  506:
    question: 'Who is the supreme overlord?'
    answer:
      - 'idra'
  57:
    question: 'What is the integral of (5x^2 -8x +5)dx'
    answer:
      - '(5x^3)/3-4x^2+5x+c'
  58:
    question: 'What is the derivative of X^3?'
    answer:
      - '3x^2'
  59:
    question: 'What is the integral of 4x^6?'
    answer:
      - '(4x^7)/6+c'
  60:
    question: 'Integrate z^7?'
    answer:
      - '(z^8)/7+c'
  61:
    question: 'Who is the father of computers?'
    answer:
      - 'Charles Babbage'
  62:
    question: 'What is 11 * 11?'
    answer:
      - '121'
  63:
    question: 'How long is an Olympic swimming pool (in meters)?'
    answer:
      - '50'
  64:
    question: 'What was the first soft drink in space?'
    answer:
      - 'Coca Cola'
  65:
    question: 'What food never goes bad?'
    answer:
      - 'Honey'
  66:
    question: 'On the farm, what is a "kid?"'
    answer:
      - 'baby goat'
  67:
    question: 'Which country says "ta" for thank you?'
    answer:
      - 'UK'
  68:
    question: 'Which country has the most natural lakes?'
    answer:
      - 'Canada'
  69:
    question: 'Which country is in South America and has an official language of Dutch?'
    answer:
      - 'Suriname'
  70:
    question: 'Which country is Area 51 located in?'
    answer:
      - 'United States'
      - 'usa'
      - 'america'
  71:
    question: 'Which country is is the Terracotta Army located in?'
    answer:
      - 'China'
  72:
    question: 'Evaluate the limit, as x approaches 2, of (8-3x+12x^2).'
    answer:
      - '50'
  73:
    question: 'Evaluate the limit, as x approaches 2, of (8 - x^3).'
    answer:
      - '0'
  74:
    question: 'Integrate the following, (x^7 +1)'
    answer:
      - '(x^8)/7+x+c'
  75:
    question: 'What signifies "significance" within a summary statistics table?'
    answer:
      - 'star'
      - 'stars'
  76:
    question: 'Evaluate 2(x-3)=4x-1?'
    answer:
      - '-2.5'

  5001:
    question: 'What is the formula for the sine rule?'
    answer:
      - 'a/sinA = b/sinB = c/sinC'

  5003:
    question: 'What instrument family does the bassoon belong to?'
    answer:
      - 'woodwind'

  5004:
    question: 'How much money does answering a trivia question give you?'
    answer:
      - '6k'
      - '6000'

  5005:
    question: 'Which composer died 6 days after the premiere of their final symphony (symphony 6)?'
    answer:
      - 'tchaikovsky'

  5006:
    question: 'Evaluate e^(i*pi*2.5).'
    answer:
      - 'i'

  5007:
    question: 'What is the full name of the FDE cycle?'
    answer:
      - 'fetch decode execute cycle'
      - 'fetch decode execute'
 
  6001:
    question: 'What was used in place of observers before they came out?'
    answer: 
      - 'BUD'
  
  6002:
    question: 'What is the state that blocks turn into when pushed by pistons?'
    answer: 
      - 'Block 46'

  6003:
    question: 'How many game ticks does a redstone tick last?'
    answer: 
      - '2'

  6004:
    question: 'How long is the delay between each activation for a dispenser in redstone ticks?'
    answer: 
      - '4'

  6005:
    question: 'How many blocks can a piston push?'
    answer: 
      - '12'

  6006:
    question: 'What does the redstone acronym BUD stand for?'
    answer: 
      - 'Block Update Detector'

  6007:
    question: 'How long of a redstone signal does a stone button last for in redstone ticks?'
    answer: 
      - '10'

  6008:
    question: 'What is an alternative name for the hopper clock?'
    answer: 
      - 'Etho Clock'

  6010:
    question: 'What type of pressure plate(s) cannot be triggered by items?'
    answer: 
      - 'Stone'

  6011:
    question: 'Can a comparator detect a composter and give a signal strength?'
    answer: 
      - 'Yes'

  6012:
    question: 'Can bedrock be obtained in vanilla survival minecraft without the use of commands or creative mode?'
    answer: 
      - 'Yes'

  6013:
    question: 'Can the Ender dragon be killed by 1 arrow?'
    answer: 
      - 'Yes'

  6014:
    question: 'What do minecraft polar bears drop?'
    answer: 
      - 'Raw cod'

  6015:
    question: 'Can a slime block be powered by redstone?'
    answer: 
      - 'Yes'

  6016:
    question: 'Can a honey block be powered by redstone?'
    answer: 
      - 'No'

  6017:
    question: 'Starting from the rail that it is powered, up to how many blocks does a powered rail extend its power?'
    answer: 
      - '9'

  6018:
    question: 'What is the max effective level of the lure enchant?'
    answer: 
      - '5'

  6019:
    question: 'What were sugarcane used to be called?'
    answer: 
      - 'reeds'

  6020:
    question: 'What are the chances of a natural pink sheep spawning'
    answer: 
      - '1%'

  6021:
    question: 'What is physically shorter, a carpet or a 2 layered snow block?'
    answer: 
      - '2 layered snow block'

  6022:
    question: 'Can cats give you phantom membranes?'
    answer: 
      - 'Yes'

  6023:
    question: 'Can cats give you diamonds?'
    answer: 
      - 'No'

  6024:
    question: 'What is the minimum amount of iron ingots that an iron golem drops?'
    answer: 
      - '3'

  6025:
    question: 'How many days without sleeping does it take before phantoms start to spawn?'
    answer: 
      - '3'

  6026:
    question: 'Can you plant mushrooms on stone?'
    answer: 
      - 'Yes'

  6027:
    question: 'How many firework stars can you add to a rocket?'
    answer: 
      - '7'

  6028:
    question: 'What has the strongest explosion?'
    answer: 
      - 'Wither'

  6029:
    question: 'Which is stronger, a charged creeper explosion or an end crystal?'
    answer: 
      - 'Neither'

  6030:
    question: 'As of 1.17, what is the highest blast resistance value?'
    asnwer: 
      - '360000.8'

  6031:
    question: 'Can TNT destroy beacons?'
    answer: 
      - 'Yes'

  6032:
    question: 'How many items can be crafted with obsidian?'
    answer: 
      - '3'

  6035:
    question: 'What block allows for instant downwards redstone?'
    answer: 
      - 'Walls'

  6036:
    question: 'How many type of heads are there in vanilla?'
    answer: 
      - '6'

  6037:
    question: 'What were emeralds used to be called?'
    answer: 
      - 'Rubies'

  6038:
    question: 'Can you apply the power enchant on a crossbow?'
    answer: 
      - 'No'

  6039:
    question: 'Can leaves trigger an observer?'
    answer: 
      - 'Yes'

  6040:
    question: 'How long is a 0-tick pulse?'
    answer: 
      - '1 tick'

  6041:
    question: 'What is the laggiest redstone component?'
    answer: 
      - 'Redstone'

  6042:
    question: 'Can you break bedrock using pistons?'
    answer: 
      - 'Yes'

  6043:
    question: 'Can mobs spawn on bedrock?'
    answer: 
      - 'No'

  6044:
    question: 'What block, other than netherrack, can keep a fire going indefinitely?'
    answer: 
      - 'Bedrock'

  6045:
    question: 'Can bone blocks generate naturally?'
    answer: 
      - 'Yes'

  6046:
    question: 'Can an observer detect a cauldron being filled up?'
    answer: 
      - 'Yes'

  6047:
    question: 'What is the most effective level of fire resistance?'
    answer: 
      - '8'

  6048:
    question: 'What is the maximum damage reduction through enchantments?'
    answer: 
      - '80%'

  6049:
    question: 'Can you fish up a feather?'
    answer: 
      - 'No'

  6050:
    question: 'Do biomes affect fishing?'
    answer: 
      - 'Yes'

  6051:
    question: 'When will Hyn finish his island?'
    answer: 
      - 'Never'